# JERRY DAVIS

#### **CONTACT**

8

Bono, AR 72416



(501)259-9109



jwdavis8589@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jerry-davis-8991641b4/



https://www.silverwindworkshop.com/



https://github.com/jwdavis1989

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Unity, Gamemaker Studio
- Systems Design
- Tabletop Game Design
- IIX
- C#
- C++
- Strong Communication Skills (Horizontal & Vertical)
- Mathematics
- Problem Solving, Performance Analysis, Debugging
- Scripting (Python & Lua)
- Git, Jira, Trello, Agile, Scrum Methodology

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Cobalt Cloud Certification Infosys
- Global Agile Developer Certification Infosys

#### **AWARDS**

- Infosys Certificate of Appreciation Going The Extra Mile
- Infosys Certificate of Excellence Rising Star

Game Designer with a successfully shipped Systems Design commercial product for the popular Dungeons & Dragons virtual tabletop, Roll20.

Accomplished Software Engineer with over 2 years of software engineering experience working with a large codebase for a renowned healthcare provider that services 4.5 million customers (1 in 9 Californians) and over 65,000 physicians.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

February 2022 - Current

# Independent Game Designer Silverwind Workshop, Remote

- Independent Game Design focused on systems design for Dungeons & Dragons 5th Edition via Roll20 Marketplace.
- Flagship product contains: Significantly improved gameplay, 29 skill trees, 65 spells, 96 items, revamped crafting, 7 example characters, and 30 art assets.
- Free demo materials available in portfolio.
- Drove 100% of Game Design, User Experience, & Graphic Design.

March 2021 - March 2023

# Senior Associate Developer BlueShield Of California Via Infosys, Remote

- Lead Software Engineer for Portal L2/L3 Support Team. Lead Software Engineer for AT5 Agile Team. JavaScript Specialist for FHIR Compliance Team.
- Developed, bug-fixed, and performed code analysis of large codebase that serves 4.5 million users and over 65,000 physicians.
- Led & Delegated tasks to team of 5 offshore software engineers, as well as providing Knowledge Transfers for Portal Support Team, Urgent Solutions Team, and Junior Associates.

November 2020 - March 2021

## Software Engineer Revature, Remote

- Developed reactive one-page web applications in React and RESTful APIs in Java Springboot using best practices.
- Drove development for several teams as both Scrum Master and Lead Developer.

## **EDUCATION**

May 2020

Bachelor of Science Computer Science Arkansas State University, Jonesboro

• Graduated with Cum Laude.